Collected
集合了
Come on, come on
集合了快点快点来集合了
How are you?
别来无恙啊
Jiang Xizhou
蒋希舟
Hurry up and perform our prepared program to the leader
赶紧给领导表演我们准备好的节目
No, no, our boss doesn't like this
别 不用我们老板不喜欢这个
Who said that
谁说的
I like it
我喜欢
Jin Feng
津枫
Brother
哥
Miss Jiang is so kind to pick me up from work
蒋小姐这么好心来接我下班呀
Mama, I only got seven fans last night
妈呀昨天晚上才涨了7个粉丝
You have to wear sunglasses when you go out tonight
今天晚上出门都得戴墨镜了
What's the matter? Yeah
怎么了这是啊
Oh, my mother
哎呀 我妈啦
Let me go on a blind date again
又让我去相亲
The old three don't work
老三样不管用啦
No
不是
The main middleman this time is Uncle Liu from Hong Kong
主要这次中间人是香港的刘叔叔
Our family is in urgent need of their support now
我们家现在急需他们的资助
Is there no way to refuse
根本没办法拒绝吗
And the family across the street
还有对面的世家
We can't be taunted either
我们也惹不起呀
Come on, stop acting
行了别演了
What do you need me to do? Say it
需要我做什么说吧
Didn't I come to see you here
我这不来找你的吗
What about me? I need you to go on a blind date for me
我呢需要你替我去相亲
Blind Date Again
又相亲
You can rest assured that the Xu family has been abroad all the year round
你放心徐家常年在国外
There is no intersection with our family
跟我们家没有任何的交集
Absolutely won't wear a gang
绝对不会穿帮
Good
好
Hello
喂
Well, maybe
嗯可能
It's a little too bad
有点太糟了
Each project team
各项目组
The team leader is ready to report the project situation to Xu in sequence
组长准备按顺序给徐总汇报项目情况
There is also Lin Yulu designer of Project b Group
还有项目b组的林玉露设计师
Please come too
麻烦也来一下
According to your orders, the report time has been arranged
按您的吩咐已经排好汇报时间了
Then you told me to buy a summer drink for everyone
然后您交代的给大家买去暑饮料
I checked the famous fruit and tea shop nearby
我查了一下附近有出名的果茶店
Would you mind pineapple tea and peach tea
您看定菠萝果茶和桃子果茶可以吗
Wait a minute
等一下
Do you order peaches?
都订桃子的吧
A good boss
好的老板
Finally, this is for you
最后是这个给您
It's the old lady who arranged a blind date for you this month
是老夫人这个月给你安排的相亲对象
The time has been arranged for you
时间已经给你排好了
The nearest one is at 7:00 tomorrow morning
最近的一个是明早7点
At 7:00 tomorrow morning
明早7点
Is this big lady going to catch up with the morning shift tomorrow
这位大小姐是要赶着明天上早班吗
This lady is in new york
这位小姐在纽约
I have booked your flight for tonight
已经给您订好今晚的飞机了
Boss
老板
I'm not saying
我不是说
That Xu was a misunderstanding yesterday
那个徐总昨天是个误会啊
I'll explain it to Xi Zhou
我会跟希舟解释清楚的
Then let the Chiang family talk to the middleman
然后让蒋家去跟中间人说
Let the Jiang family tell the middleman that the two sides meet
让蒋家跟中间人说双方见面
Everyone thinks it's good
都觉得不错
Ah, right, right, right
啊对对对
No, boss. What do you mean
不对老板您什么意思啊
You did a good job
你演的还不错
Let's play it for another two months
再演两个月吧
With what
凭什么呀
You can have a look at my weekly newspaper
您可以看一下我的周报
I work a lot
我工作很多的
There is no time to play house with you
没有时间陪您过家家
Then I can only tell the middleman
那我就只能跟中间人说
Jiang family
蒋家
I found a little girl to fool me instead of Jiang Xizhou
找了个小姑娘来代替蒋希舟糊弄我
The most important thing is
最重要的是
Be sure to let the other party reject the middleman
一定要让对方拒绝中间人
Boss, what do I think
老板我觉得呢
My work is not saturated enough
我的工作还不够饱和
There is still room to work hard
还有能努力的空间
Go home with me to see grandma that weekend
那周末回家陪我去看奶奶
Do you have an appointment tonight
今晚有约吗
Overtime
加班
Let's work overtime in a different way
换个方式加班吧
jeishu
jeishu